<resources>
    <!--Application used strings -->
    <string name="app_name">NonEstDeus</string>
    <string name="title_random">Random</string>
    <string name="title_by_number">By Number</string>
    <string name="title_by_author">By Author</string>
    <string name="title_license">License</string>
    <string name="title_send_feedback"> Feedback</string>
    <string name="quoteNum">000</string>
    <string name="quoteText">This is some test quote text so that something displays on the screen.</string>
    <string name="authorText">Me myself and I</string>
    <string name="buttonText">Get a random quote.</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="opening_toast_text">Welcome to Non est deus Atheist Quotes App!</string>
    <string name="clip_description_label">Non est deus quote</string>
    <string name="clipboard_copy_toast">Copied to Clipboard</string>
    <string name="error_occurred">Some error occurred. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="license">NonEstDeus App. Ver. %s \n\nCopyright © 2018, Patrick Leonard\n\nThis software is provided \'as is\' and without any express or implied warranties, including, but no limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose are disclaimed.\n\nNonEstDeus is an open source project. The source code for NonEstDeus can be found, with license, on Github:\nhttps://github.com/PatrickLeonard/NonEstDeus</string>
    <string name="actionbar_subtitle">Atheism Quotes</string>
    <string name="change_color_palette">Colors</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">283909378905424</string>

    <!--Quotes -->
    <string name="dawkins_quote_1">We are all atheists about most of the gods that humanity has ever believed in. Some of us just go one god further.</string>
    <string name="douglas_adams_author">Douglas Adams</string>
    <string name="douglas_adams_quote_1">Isn\'t it enough to see that a garden is beautiful without having to believe that there are fairies at the bottom of it too?</string>
    <string name="hitchens_quote_1">That which can be asserted without evidence, can be dismissed without evidence.</string>
    <string name="voltaire_quote_1">Those who can make you believe absurdities, can make you commit atrocities.</string>
    <string name="asimov_quote_1">Properly read, the Bible is the most potent force for atheism ever conceived.</string>
    <string name="napoleon_quote_1">Religion is excellent stuff for keeping common people quiet. Religion is what keeps the poor from murdering the rich.</string>
    <string name="epicurus_quote_1">Is God willing to prevent evil, but not able?\nThen he is not omnipotent.\nIs he able, but not willing?\nThen he is malevolent.\nIs he both able and willing?\n Then whence cometh evil?\nIs he neither able nor willing?\nThen why call him God?</string>
    <string name="carlin_quote_1">Atheism is a non-prophet organization.</string>
    <string name="twain_quote_1">The Bible has noble poetry in it… and some good morals and a wealth of obscenity, and upwards of a thousand lies.</string>
    <string name="hitchens_quote_2">Human decency is not derived from religion. It precedes it.</string>
    <string name="pirsig_quote_1">When one person suffers from a delusion, it is called insanity. When many people suffer from a delusion it is called a Religion.</string>
    <string name="colbert_quote_1">Agnostics are just atheists without balls.</string>
    <string name="vonnegut_quote_1">I am a humanist, which means, in part, that I have tried to behave decently without expectations of rewards or punishments after I am dead.</string>
    <string name="tom_wolfe_quote_1">A cult is a religion with no political power.</string>
    <string name="neil_degrasse_tyson_quote_1">The more I learn about the universe, the less convinced I am that there\'s any sort of benevolent force that has anything to do with it, at all.</string>
    <string name="murakami_quote_1">If you think God\'s there, He is. If you don\'t, He isn\'t. And if that\'s what God\'s like, I wouldn\'t worry about it.</string>
    <string name="zola_quote_1">Civilization will not attain to its perfection until the last stone from the last church falls on the last priest.</string>
    <string name="pryor_quote_1">The reason people use a crucifix against vampires is because vampires are allergic to bullshit.</string>
    <string name="sagan_quote_1">I don\'t want to believe. I want to know.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_1">We have a choice. We have two options as human beings. We have a choice between conversation and war. That\'s it. Conversation and violence. And faith is a conversation stopper.</string>
    <string name="roddenberry_quote_1">We must question the story logic of having an all-knowing all-powerful God, who creates faulty Humans, and then blames them for his own mistakes.</string>
    <string name="lewis_black_quote_1">Who knew that the devil had a factory where he made millions of fossils, which his minions distributed throughout the earth, in order to confuse my tiny brain?</string>
    <string name="einstein_quote_1">I don\'t try to imagine a personal God; it suffices to stand in awe at the structure of the world, insofar as it allows our inadequate senses to appreciate it.</string>
    <string name="ruth_green_quote_1">There was a time when religion ruled the world. It is known as the Dark Ages.</string>
    <string name="lincoln_quote_1">The Bible is not my book nor Christianity my profession. I could never give assent to the long, complicated statements of Christian dogma.</string>
    <string name="richard_morgan_quote_1">A preoccupation with the next world clearly shows an inability to cope credibly with this one.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_2">Theology is ignorance with wings.</string>
    <string name="duhamel_quote_1">I have too much respect for the idea of God to make it responsible for such an absurd world.</string>
    <string name="marquis_de_sade_quote_1">To judge from the notions expounded by theologians, one must conclude that God created most men simply with a view to crowding hell.</string>
    <string name="ruth_green_quote_2">I studied every page of this book, and I didn\'t find enough love to fill a salt shaker. God is not love in the Bible; God is vengeance, from Alpha to Omega.</string>
    <string name="john_c_wright_quote_1">If atheism solved all human woe, then the Soviet Union would have been an empire of joy and dancing bunnies, instead of the land of corpses.</string>
    <string name="bakunin_quote_1">If God really existed, it would be necessary to abolish Him.</string>
    <string name="twain_quote_2">Nothing exists but you. And you are but a thought.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_3">Religious moderation is the product of secular knowledge and scriptural ignorance.</string>
    <string name="gervais_quote_1">You won\'t burn in hell. But be nice anyway.</string>
    <string name="jong_quote_1">Without the gods, how would I sing?\' I asked.\n\'With your own voice,\' he said.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_4">The problem with religion, because it\'s been sheltered from criticism, is that it allows people to believe en masse what only idiots or lunatics could believe in isolation.</string>
    <string name="ingersoll_quote_1">And why does this same God tell me how to raise my children when he had to drown his?</string>
    <string name="gore_vidal_quote_1">To a born-again atheist like myself, it is clear that each of us has multiple selves, talents, perceptions. But to the Roman Catholic, unity is all.</string>
    <string name="madison_quote_1">Religious bondage shackles and debilitates the mind, and unfits it for every noble enterprise, every expanded prospect.</string>
    <string name="bill_gates_quote_1">Just in terms of allocation of time resources, religion is not very efficient. There`s a lot more I could be doing on a Sunday morning.</string>
    <string name="brad_pitt_quote_1">I\'m probably 20 percent atheist and 80 percent agnostic. I don\'t think anyone really knows. You\'ll either find out or not when you get there, until then there\'s no point thinking about it.</string>
    <string name="jethro_tull_quote_1">In the beginning Man created God; and in the image of Man created he him.</string>
    <string name="jeni_quote_1">You\'re basically killing each other to see who\'s got the better imaginary friend.</string>
    <string name="ruth_green_quote_3">Today evolution of human intelligence has advanced us to the stage where most of us are too smart to invent new gods but are reluctant to give up the old1 ones.</string>
    <string name="neil_degrasse_tyson_quote_2">God is an ever receding pocket of scientific ignorance.</string>
    <string name="stanton_quote_1">The bible and the church have been the greatest stumbling block in the way of women\'s emancipation.</string>
    <string name="almaarri_quote_1">The inhabitants of the earth are of two sorts: those with brains, but no religion, and those with religion, but no brains.</string>
    <string name="dholdbach_quote_1">If the ignorance of nature gave birth to such a variety of gods, the knowledge of this nature is calculated to destroy them.</string>
    <string name="ingersoll_quote_2">As more people become more intelligent they care less for preachers and more for teachers.</string>
    <string name="penn_jillette_quote_1">You don\'t have to be brave or a saint, a martyr, or even very smart to be an atheist. All you have to be able to say is \'I don\'t know.\'</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_5">The faith of religion is belief on insufficient evidence.</string>
    <string name="dershowitz_quote_1">I have always considered \"Pascal\'s Wager\" a questionable bet to place, since any God worth believing in would prefer an honest agnostic to a calculating hypocrite.</string>
    <string name="penn_jillette_quote_2">Once you\'ve condoned faith in general, you\'ve condoned any crazy shit done because of faith.</string>
    <string name="ruth_green_quote_4">The natural is so awesome that we need not go beyond it.</string>
    <string name="dholdbach_quote_2">All children are atheists, they have no idea of God.</string>
    <string name="powers_quote_1">If god created man in his own image, how come I\'m not invisible?</string>
    <string name="sage_quote_2">It is said that men may not be the dreams of the god, but rather that the gods are the dreams of men.</string>
    <string name="ingersoll_quote_3">The hands that help are better far than lips that pray.</string>
    <string name="andy_rooney_quote_1">I\'d be more willing to accept religion, even if I didn\'t believe it, if I thought it made people nicer to each other but I don\'t think it does.</string>
    <string name="mehta_quote_1">Nothing draws people more quickly away from religion than an open mind.</string>
    <string name="smith_ready_quote_1">Go ahead, God, you fat, filthy motherfucker, lightning-bolt my ass into oblivion if you\'re so tough!</string>
    <string name="ingersoll_quote_4">The religionist is a living fossil, embedded in that rock called faith.</string>
    <string name="andy_rooney_quote_2">Christians talk as though goodness was their idea but good behavior doesn\'t have any religious origin. Our prisons are filled with the devout.</string>
    <string name="penn_jillette_quote_3">Love and respect all people. Hate and destroy all faith.</string>
    <string name="voltaire_quote_2">All men are born with a nose and ten fingers, but no one was born with a knowledge of God.</string>
    <string name="amis_quote_1">Religious belief is without reason and without dignity, and its record is near-universally dreadful.</string>
    <string name="gervais_quote_2">A Christian telling an atheist they\'re going to hell is as scary as a child telling an adult they\'re not getting any presents from Santa.</string>
    <string name="cox_quote_1">Saying that you are moral because you believe in a god is like saying you are an economist because you play monopoly.</string>
    <string name="andy_rooney_quote_3">I don\'t differentiate much, except in degree, between people who believe in religion from those who believe in astrology, magic or the supernatural.</string>
    <string name="bertrand_russel_quote_1">The idea that things must have a beginning is really due to the poverty of our imagination.</string>
    <string name="tochukwu_quote_1">Blessed are the doubters: for they shall not be easily fooled.</string>
    <string name="neil_degrasse_tyson_quote_3">I\'d ask [God] why he keeps trying to kill us all with disease, pestilence, and natural disasters. I\'d ask why 99% of all species there ever were are now extinct — if God works in mysterious ways, that way is mysteriously genocidal.</string>
    <string name="navabi_quote_1">If God creates morality, then morality is nothing more than the whimsy of a divine being blindly followed by humans.</string>
    <string name="navabi_quote_2">Scriptures may have grains of historical truth within them, but there is also ample hyperbole, speculation and mythology.</string>
    <string name="mcclennan_quote_1">When an atheist is born, a kitten kills a god.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_6">The only differences between a cult and a religion are the numbers of adherents and the degree to which they are marginalized by the rest of society.</string>
    <string name="navabi_quote_3">Not knowing the answer to a question is not a valid excuse for making up a fairytale to explain it.</string>
    <string name="navabi_quote_4">There is no evidence to suggest that God helps people. There is, however, ample evidence that people can help themselves and each other.</string>
    <string name="culliton_quote_1">Nothing in any religious teachings goes beyond Humanism, unless you add the supernatural…Make believe is the only difference between being human and being religious.</string>
    <string name="shaha_quote_1">Religion allows people to ignore the needs of real beings in favour of the supposed wishes of a being that does not exist.</string>
    <string name="robert_jordan_quote_1">To believe a thing is not to make it true.</string>
    <string name="dawkins_quote_2">Religion is a distraction from true education.</string>
    <string name="dawkins_quote_3">There was something built into the human brain by natural selection which was once useful, and which now manifests itself as religion.</string>
    <string name="cj_anderson_quote_1">Where human knowledge ends the imagined God begins.</string>
    <string name="kudari_quote_1">Coincidentally, the words RELIGION and BULLSHIT both have eight letters.</string>
    <string name="stephen_fry_quote_1">You can\'t just say there is a god because the world is beautiful. You have to account for bone cancer in children.</string>
    <string name="amit_gupta_quote_1"><![CDATA["Whenever I see all around , I see nothing except atoms & molecules "]]></string>
    <string name="steven_weinberg_quote_1">Religion is an insult to human dignity. With or without religion, you would have good people doing good things and evil people doing evil things. But for good people to do evil things, that takes religion?</string>
    <string name="darrow_quote_1">I believe that religion is the belief in future life and in God. I don\'t believe in either. I don\'t believe in God as I don\'t believe in Mother Goose.</string>
    <string name="percy_shelley_quote_1">God is an hypothesis, and, as such, stands in need of proof: the onus probandi rests on the theist.</string>
    <string name="schrodinger_quote_1">By the way, I never realized that to be nonbelieving, to be an atheist, was a thing to be proud of. It went without saying as it were.</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_quote_7">Atheism is not a philosophy; it is not even a view of the world; it is simply an admission of the obvious.</string>
    <string name="molyneux_quote_1">I don\'t think it is a good mental health practice to fantasize that you know the infinite thoughts of imaginary entities.</string>
    <string name="holyoake_quote_1">Atheism deprives superstition of its stand ground, and compels Theism to reason for its existence.</string>
    <string name="laertius_quote_1">As to the gods, I have no means of knowing either that they exist or do not exist. For many are the obstacles that impede knowledge, both the obscurity of the question and the shortness of human life.</string>
    <string name="charles_chaplan_quote_1">By simple common sense I don\'t believe in God, in none.</string>
    <string name="tennesse_williams_quote_1">All your Western theologies, the whole mythology of them, are based on the concept of God as a senile delinquent</string>
    <string name="amis_quote_2">It\'s possible to be flippant here, when Jihadists fly aircraft into buildings they shout God is Great, what do atheists shout when they do it?</string>
    <string name="chomsky_quote_1">…if you ask me whether or not I\'m an atheist, I wouldn\'t even answer. I would first want an explanation of what it is that I\'m supposed not to believe in, and I\'ve never seen an explanation.</string>
    <string name="hepburn_quote_1">I am an atheist and that\'s it. I believe there\'s nothing we can know except that we should be kind to each other and do what we can for other people.</string>
    <string name="wozniak_quote_1">I am also atheist or agnostic (I don\'t even know the difference). I\'ve never been to church and prefer to think for myself.</string>

    <!--Authors -->
    <string name="chomsky_author">Noam Chomsky</string>
    <string name="wozniak_author">Steve Wozniak</string>
    <string name="hepburn_author">Katharine Hepburn</string>
    <string name="tennesse_willaims_author">Tennessee Williams</string>
    <string name="charles_chaplin_author">Charles Chaplin</string>
    <string name="laertius_author">Diogenes Laertius</string>
    <string name="holyoake_author">George Holyoake</string>
    <string name="molyneux_author">Stefan Molyneux</string>
    <string name="schrodinger_author">Erwin Schrodinger</string>
    <string name="percy_shelley_author">Percy Bysshe Shelley</string>
    <string name="darrow_author">Clarence Darrow</string>
    <string name="steven_weinberg_author">Steven Weinberg</string>
    <string name="amit_gupta_author">Amit Gupta</string>
    <string name="stephen_fry_author">Stephen Fry</string>
    <string name="kudari_author">Daya Kudari</string>
    <string name="cj_anderson_author">C.J. Anderson</string>
    <string name="robert_jordan_author">Robert Jordan</string>
    <string name="jeni_author">Richard Jeni</string>
    <string name="jethro_tull_author">Jethro Tull</string>
    <string name="brad_pitt_author">Brad Pitt</string>
    <string name="bill_gates_author">Bill Gates</string>
    <string name="madison_author">James Madison</string>
    <string name="gore_vidal_author">Gore Vidal</string>
    <string name="ingersoll_author">Robert G. Ingersoll</string>
    <string name="jong_author">Erica Jong</string>
    <string name="gervais_author">Ricky Gervais</string>
    <string name="bakunin_author">Mikhail Bakunin</string>
    <string name="john_c_wright_author">John C. Wright</string>
    <string name="marquis_de_sade_author">Marquis de Sade</string>
    <string name="duhamel_author">Georges Duhamel</string>
    <string name="richard_morgan_author">Richard K. Morgan</string>
    <string name="lincoln_author">Abraham Lincoln</string>
    <string name="ruth_green_author">Ruth Hurmence Green</string>
    <string name="einstein_author">Albert Einstein</string>
    <string name="lewis_black_author">Lewis Black</string>
    <string name="roddenberry_author">Gene Roddenberry</string>
    <string name="sam_harris_author">Sam Harris</string>
    <string name="sagan_author">Carl Sagan</string>
    <string name="pryor_author">Richard Pryor</string>
    <string name="zola_author">Emile Zola</string>
    <string name="murakami_author">Haruki Murakami</string>
    <string name="neil_degrasse_tyson_author">Neil deGrasse Tyson</string>
    <string name="tom_wolfe_author">Tom Wolfe</string>
    <string name="vonnegut_author">Kurt Vonnegut</string>
    <string name="colbert_author">Stephen Colbert</string>
    <string name="author_pirsig">Robert M. Pirsig</string>
    <string name="twain_author">Mark Twain</string>
    <string name="carlin_author">George Carlin</string>
    <string name="epicurus_author">Epicurus</string>
    <string name="napoleon_author">Napoleon Bonaparte</string>
    <string name="asimov_author">Isaac Asimov</string>
    <string name="dawkins_author">Richard Dawkins</string>
    <string name="hitchens_author">Christopher Hitchens</string>
    <string name="voltaire_author">Voltaire</string>
    <string name="shaha_author">Alom Shaha</string>
    <string name="culliton_author">Travis Culliton</string>
    <string name="mcclennan_author">C.P. McClennan</string>
    <string name="navabi_author">Armin Navabi</string>
    <string name="tochukwu_author">Aniekee Tochukwu</string>
    <string name="bertrand_russell_author">Bertrand Russell</string>
    <string name="cox_author">Robert W. Cox</string>
    <string name="amis_author">Martin Amis</string>
    <string name="smith_ready_author">Jeri Smith-Ready</string>
    <string name="mehta_author">Hemant Mehta</string>
    <string name="andy_rooney_author">Andy Rooney</string>
    <string name="powers_author">David Powers</string>
    <string name="dershowitz_author">Alan M. Dershowitz</string>
    <string name="penn_jillette_author">Penn Jillette</string>
    <string name="dholdbach_author">Paul Henry Thiry d\'Holbach</string>
    <string name="stanton_author">Elizabeth Cady Stanton</string>
    <string name="almaarri_author">Al-Ma\'arri</string>

    <string-array name="red_fuzz_smoke_storm">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#000000</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#E5C3C3</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#D86C6C</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#F7F2F2</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#FFCCCC</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="azure_black_sea_serpent">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#040F0F</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#51BCBC</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#1C4949</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#D4F4F4</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#A1EAEA</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="platinum_pastel_power_burgundy">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#424242</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#AEA4BF</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#3B252C</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#E3E4DB</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#CDCDCD</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mantis_mint_tea_apple">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#337733</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#B2D89E</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#009900</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#CAEFB6</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#9DE577</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="jungle_acajou_peach_ochre_mustard">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#1B2021</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#EFC69B</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#481D24</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#E9724C</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#FFC857</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grey_redwood_taupe_raisin">
        <!--Title Text Color-->
        <item>#9B5852</item>
        <!--Toolbar/Navigation Bar Background Color-->
        <item>#D7CDCC</item>
        <!--Quote Text Color-->
        <item>#2B1D1C</item>
        <!--Quote Background Color-->
        <item>#705B59</item>
        <!--List Fragment Item Background Color-->
        <item>#FFFFFF</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="theme_titles">
        <item>Theme 1</item>
        <item>Theme 2</item>
        <item>Theme 3</item>
        <item>Theme 4</item>
        <item>Theme 5</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
